softsurroundingsoutlet.com 2016-04-28

# Soft Surroundings - Customer Care - Privacy Policy & Terms Of Use'

**Privacy Policy & Terms of Use**

Last updated: February 2, 2016

We appreciate the trust you place in Soft Surroundings, and we are committed to respecting your privacy and the security of your personal information. Our privacy policy describes the information we collect and how we use it. SoftSurroundings.com and SoftSurroundingsOutlet.com are owned by Triad Catalog Co., LLC. Every effort has been made to check our information for accuracy. Descriptive or typographical errors are subject to correction.

We always welcome your questions and feedback. For privacy-related issues, please contact us at:

Soft Surroundings  
1100 N Lindbergh Blvd   
St. Louis, MO 63132   
Phone: 1-800-240-7076   
Fax: 1-314-521-5780   

**Information We Collect**  
We may collect the following information: first and last name, street address, city, telephone number, e-mail address and, when necessary, credit card information, when you: 

  * Place an order from our catalogs or on our website
  * Make a purchase at one of our retail stores
  * Return an item or make an exchange
  * Inquire about our services
  * Request a catalog
  * Receive a gift package
  * Create an account at SoftSurroundings.com or SoftSurroundingsOutlet.com
  * Subscribe to our e-newsletters or e-mail promotions
  * Enter a contest or sweepstakes
  * Are referred to us through a marketing promotion
  * Participate in a marketing survey, promotion or event

We maintain the data that you provide us, along with a record of your purchases, in a secure database. 

**Using Information We Collect**   
At Soft Surroundings, we always want to provide you with the best possible shopping experience and fulfill your orders exactly as you've requested. In order to do this, we collect information that allows us to: 

  * Process and track your order
  * Provide the services you request
  * Contact you about the status of an order
  * Send you catalogs or promotional offers we believe will be of interest to you
  * Send you e-mail promotions
  * Identify your product and service preferences
  * Customize our communications to you
  * Provide information concerning product recalls or products you have purchased
  * Improve our merchandise selection and customer service

**Information We Share with Others**  
We contract with other companies to provide certain services, including credit card processing, affiliate marketing and shipping. We provide these companies with only the information they need to perform their services and work closely with them to ensure that your privacy is respected and protected. These companies are prohibited by contract from using this information for their own marketing purposes or from sharing this information with anyone other than Soft Surroundings.

From time to time, we make our mailing list (names and addresses only) and general shopping activity available to carefully screened companies whose products we believe will be of interest to you. If you prefer that we do not share any information with these companies, please contact us at:

Soft Surroundings   
1100 N Lindbergh Blvd   
St. Louis, MO 63132   
Phone: 1-800-240-7076   
Fax: 1-314-521-5780   

On rare occasions, we may disclose specific information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, or when required by law to do so. We may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes.

**Your Choices**  
We offer choices about the types of information you receive from us. If you prefer not to receive catalogs or other communications from Soft Surroundings, please contact us at:

Soft Surroundings   
1100 N Lindbergh Blvd   
St. Louis, MO 63132   
Phone: 1-800-240-7076   
Fax: 1-314-521-5780   

If you no longer wish to receive our e-newsletters and e-mail promotions you may electronically [unsubscribe here](https://www.softsurroundingsoutlet.com/FAQ/E-mail/Unsubscribe_from_E-mail/) or contact us at:

Soft Surroundings   
1100 N Lindbergh Blvd   
St. Louis, MO 63132   
Phone: 1-800-240-7076   
Fax: 1-314-521-5780   

If you do not want to receive mailings from other carefully screened companies, please contact us at:

Soft Surroundings   
1100 N Lindbergh Blvd   
St. Louis, MO 63132   
Phone: 1-800-240-7076   
Fax: 1-314-521-5780   

Please be sure to provide us your exact name and address, or the mailing label from your catalog, so that we can be sure to identify you correctly. Because we plan our mailings in advance, it may take several weeks for your request to become effective. If you continue to receive our communications, please contact us again and we will make every effort to correct the situation.

**Cookies and Pixel Tags**  
A cookie is a small data file that is stored by your Web browser on your computer. Cookies enable you to place an order on our website. 

If you set your browser to refuse cookies, please call us at 1-800-240-7076 to place your order.

We also use cookies and pixel tags (tiny graphic images) to tell us what parts of our website you have visited. Pixel tags also enable us to send you e-mail in a format you can read and let us know when you have opened an e-mail message from us.

We also may contract with other companies who use cookies or other online tools such as pixel tags to measure the performance of a marketing effort on our behalf. We may share your personally identifiable information, including your name, address, email address, as well as a record of any transactions you conduct on our website or offline with us with a third-party advertising partner and its service providers in order to deliver to you banner advertisements and other advertising tailored to your interests when you visit certain websites. Our advertising partner will make the data we provide it anonymous. To choose not to have this information used by our third-party advertising partner, [click here.](http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

We prohibit these companies from using this information for their own marketing purposes or from sharing this information with anyone other than Soft Surroundings.

 **California Privacy Rights**  
Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83, Soft Surroundings customers living in the State of California can request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. For requests, please contact Soft Surroundings via the contact information below.

**How We Use E-mail**   
When you provide us your e-mail address, we may send you e-mails necessary to process your order or respond to a request. For example, after you place an order at SoftSurroundings.com and SoftSurroundingsOutlet.com, you will receive an e-mail confirmation and, in most cases, an e-mail with delivery tracking information.

**Links to Other Sites**   
Occasionally we provide links on our website to other sites we think you will enjoy. These sites operate independently of Soft Surroundings and have established their own privacy and security policies. For the best online experience, we strongly encourage you to review the policies at any site you visit.

**Updating or Reviewing Your Information**  
To update your customer information (name, address, telephone number and e-mail address), please contact us at:

Soft Surroundings   
1100 N Lindbergh Blvd   
St. Louis, MO 63132   
Phone: 1-800-240-7076   
Fax: 1-314-521-5780   

A limited amount of purchase information also may be available to you. To protect your privacy, we will need to validate your identity before you update or review your information.

**Security**  
It is our intent to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you. We use a variety of current technologies and processes for protection of our customer data. We limit the information we provide to outside companies with whom we contract to only what they need to carry out their responsibilities.

When you make a purchase, request a catalog or create an account on our website, your transactional information is transmitted in a safe, encrypted format. See [Secure Online Shopping](https://www.softsurroundingsoutlet.com/FAQ/Ordering/Secure_Online_Shopping/) for details.

**Privacy of Children on Our Website**  
Our website is not intended for use by children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

**Policy Changes**  
From time to time, we may use customer information for unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change, we will post these changes on our website. We encourage you to review our privacy policy periodically.

**Questions or Comments?**  
For questions, comments or assistance, we invite you to contact us at:

Soft Surroundings   
1100 N Lindbergh Blvd   
St. Louis, MO 63132   
Phone: 1-800-240-7076   
Fax: 1-314-521-5780
